[
  {
    "question": "What is a prefix?",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "A word added at the end of a base word",
    "optionB": "A word added at the beginning of a base word",
    "optionC": "A word that means the opposite of another word",
    "optionD": "A word that changes the tense of a verb",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "B. A word added at the beginning of a base word",
    "explanation": "Prefix is something which can be added to the beginning of a word to modify or change its meaning.",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following words has a suffix?",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "Unhappy",
    "optionB": "Help",
    "optionC": "Jumping",
    "optionD": "Table",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "C. Jumping",
    "explanation": "Suffix is attached to the end of the word.",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the prefix \"mis-\" usually mean?",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "To do again",
    "optionB": "Not or opposite of",
    "optionC": "Before",
    "optionD": "Very",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "B. Not or opposite of",
    "explanation": "\"mis\" means not or opposite of.",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following words has a prefix and a suffix?",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "Running",
    "optionB": "Quickly",
    "optionC": "Unhappily",
    "optionD": "Friendly",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "C. Unhappily",
    "explanation": "Prefix attached to the start of the word and suffix attached to the end of the word.",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the suffix in the word \"happiness\"?",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "hap",
    "optionB": "ness",
    "optionC": "iness",
    "optionD": "happy",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "B. ness",
    "explanation": "\"Happy\" is the root word.",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the prefix \"pre-\" usually mean?",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "Not or opposite of",
    "optionB": "After",
    "optionC": "Before",
    "optionD": "Very",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "C. Before",
    "explanation": "\"Pre\" means before.",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the suffix in the word \"careless\"?",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "less",
    "optionB": "care",
    "optionC": "lessca",
    "optionD": "ful",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "A. less",
    "explanation": "\"Care\" is the root word.",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the prefix \"re-\" usually mean?",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "To do again",
    "optionB": "Not or opposite of",
    "optionC": "Before",
    "optionD": "Very",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "A. To do again",
    "explanation": "\"Re\" means something that is going to happen again.",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following words has a prefix that means \"between\" or \"among\"?",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "Submarine",
    "optionB": "Interact",
    "optionC": "Prehistoric",
    "optionD": "Uncommon",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "B. Interact",
    "explanation": "\"Inter\" means between or among.",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following words has a suffix that means \"state or quality\"",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "Jumped",
    "optionB": "Teacher",
    "optionC": "Quickness",
    "optionD": "Playing",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "C. Quickness",
    "explanation": "\"Quickness\" represents a quality or an idea.",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  }
]
